PAULINA WDOWICZ

JUNIOR MANUAL TESTER

+ 48 534 068 439 paulina.wdowicz1@gmail.com https://github.com/PaulinaWdowicz https://linkedin.com/in/paulina-wdowicz

ABOUT ME

During my engineering studies at Warsaw University of Technology, I was a part of WUT Students' Council, where I got invaluable experience in student project planning and execution. Since graduation, I have worked in the field of waste management in the two largest waste management companies in Warsaw. My position required me to be precise, to pay attention to details and to meet deadlines.

Currently, I work as a manual software tester, where I am responsible for, among others: testing manual desktop applications, reporting errors, designing and creating scripts to automate testing in LUA and preparing test documentation.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- LUA basic level
- PYTHON basic level
- SQL basic level

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **EASY REDMINE** intermediate level
- JIRA basic level
- MANTIS basic level
- QUANTUM GIS basic level
- **ARCGIS** intermediate level

COURSES AND TRAININGS

- Fundamentals of Software Testing QATestLab
- Manual Software Testing Basics Udemy
- Jira Beginners Course Project Management Udemy
- Introduction to SQL: Data Management and Querying Khan Academy

LANGUGAES

- ENGLISH intermediate level (B2 certificate)
- RUSSIAN beginner
- **POLISH** mother language

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR TESTER

06. 2023 - now | CYBID

- Performing functional, regression and exploratory tests to detect defects and ensure compliance with software requirements.
- Creating and maintaining test scenarios and test occurrences.
- Documenting test results in Easy Redmine, reporting errors and working with developers to resolve them.
- Designing, developing and maintaining scripts that automate the testing process in LUA.
- Creating programs that automate testing in LUA, which are part of the testing process and reduce access time to perform regression tests.
- Preparing and updating test documentation in Markdown, including reports, test confirmation and test scenario confirmation.

ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION AND SERVICE SPECIALIST

07.2022 - 06.2023 | "BYŚ" Wojciech Byśkiniewicz

WASTE MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

01.2019 - 06.2022 | Miejskie Przedsiębiorstwo Oczyszczania Sp.z o.o. w m. st. Warszawie

MEMBER

01.2015 - 01.2019 | The Warsaw University of Technology Students' Council

EDUCATION

Warsaw University of Technology Faculty of Building Services, Hydro and Environmental Engineering

10.2013 - 09.2019 | Environmental Protection course - Bachelor (BSc.) + Master (MSc.) degree

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).